Yes, on location flying a few kilometers away from the skies of Port Edwards... Oh, we’re live?
A lot of black smoke is rising from Port Edwards. In the skies above it,
the shapes of countless fighters that sortied from both the Neucom and General Resource corporations’ bases are... oh!
It’s another explosion! What a dreadful sound that was! Everyone, if my voice reaches...
Yes, this is the studio. To sum up the reports here once more, we will repeat that.
This afternoon, at Port Edwards, USEA, General Resource and Neucom have broken into a state of hostilities.
And that battle is still ongoing. The NUN—the Neo United Nations, in order to resolve the situation, has decided to dispatch UPEO’s peacekeeping forces...
On General Resource-affiliated news outlets,
there was an announcement that at present, keyword censorship for broadcast contents has been included in delivery systems.
A large-scale restriction of the press like this being enforced is a first.
This current program is being broadcast from an independent personal base station.
That being the case, here you will see our independently-received images uncensored.
We already possess the technology for the purpose of allowing all mankind to exceed its limits, and are preparing it.
—cast aside the flesh! This is a revolution done to set lives free. And now, we will declare.
Sublimation of all mankind—that is the one and only truth that will advance our lives into a new generation!
This technology is not a dream. Perhaps we should show you a piece of evidence. —Dision!
This man, due to a General Resource trick 10 years ago, completely lost his flesh.
...and yet, as a life in the Electrosphere, he certainly exists even now.
Indeed, the “Will”, organized by the powers that came to be called by the names of “Life”, “Mind”, and “Consciousness” which we all equally hide from the start,
made not a limit of the frail existence known as Flesh and such, after all.
And this truth we came to hand down as information from prehistoric times.
We need not look back to history——. As for the existence of Life without the limit of Flesh, we transformed in this way.
That is, “the new image of mankind.” And so, above human history, Dision was reborn into the first life without flesh.
We install him as the Leader of the Beginning, and put this revolution into action!
Well now, let us, we the Ouroboros, introduce our leader, Abyssal Dision.
Our rise to action, many people still seem to be misunderstanding.
Certainly, the things people are seeing at the present point are little more than that mutual killing so familiar to mankind, after all.
However, that is all we shall say for now. The forces that the organizations known as General Resource, Neucom, and UPEO and
the war they carry out even now, are the entrances for the revolution we hope for.
Indeed, for us, the true enemies are not the powers known as General Resource and Neucom, much less UPEO and such.
When this revolution is complete, what we, no, all mankind will grasp will not be powers like these at all.
Alright, listen up. I absolutely will not admit it. There’s no way that guy is that Dision.
That was not the Dision I... well, my buddy. He was General’s ace. He was my close friend.
My, my.... —it’s someone else. The guy already died somewhere. That was not him.
Therefore—the thing that carries his name, I will without fail, with these hands... eliminate from this world. Without fail——.
Since Dision’s uprising, the war situation has been precipitously deteriorating.
Taking advantage of the chaos, Neucom is gathering an armada at Megafloat;
at the same time, war plane formations are also also being confirmed.
This mission will be to annihilate these war assets. We have deployed the cutting-edge fighter “Game”.
Furthermore, due to the deterioration of the war situation, information from the front lines is complicated;
there are concerns that we will be unable to give sufficient support from here on out.
Every one of you, we want you to exercise caution.
No matter what it takes, I’ll take that guy out, see if I don’t!
Crap!! It’s full of small fry. I won’t even be able to touch him!
If it’s come to this, I have no choice but to compete with you for downs!
Hey now, don’t you crash before me!
Good morning. Is it over? Who built this, and for what purpose...? We only have to get those men involved. Hey-y, that’s enough. WHO ARE YOU? Good morning. Well, you should know this world. WHATd you do to me? Hey now... look. It’s looking this way. In... 30 seconds. WHY? I’M not DEAD yet.... Your copy is starting up over there. Is it over yet? Can you see me? YOU’RE NOT ME. WHO ARE YOU? Can you see me? STOP IT! STOP IT! Can you see me? Run away! Can you see me? Not DEAD yet.... Can you see me? We meet again.
What happened!? Fly more carefully!! Do you want to die!?
A Neucom armada amassed at Megafloat. Attack these mobile squadrons immediately!
Neucom’s military power has been drastically weakened. —a magnificent military feat.
Great stuff! And you beat me in numbers shot down over the course of that battle.
Somehow, it seems I let that dealy with the guy blow my top way too far, too.
Thanks to you, I’ve calmed down a bit. But... hey. I’m still going to make sure to settle my score with him.
And that’s it; don’t you forget it.